retaildive.com 2017-10-31

# Privacy Policy - Industry Dive

### PRIVACY POLICY

#### Effective Date: 28 November 2016

This privacy policy explains how Industry Dive Inc. (“we,” “us,” “our”), affiliates, and subsidiaries, will collect, use, and share the information that you provide to us through your use of our mobile applications and websites that link to this privacy policy (collectively, our “Properties”). Below is a summary of the key provisions in our privacy policy. We encourage you to read the full privacy policy to understand our information practices.

When you use our Properties or otherwise interact with us, you may provide personal information (such as contact information). We may also receive personal information about you from third parties. We may collect or allow third parties to collect non-personal information including, for example, information about how you use our Properties and information about your device such as your IP address and location data. To learn more about the information that we collect, please click here.

We may use personal and non-personal information for a variety of purposes, including to maintain security, improve our business, personalize your experience with our Properties, and deliver more relevant advertising. To learn more about how we use your information, please click here.

We may share personal information that we collect with third parties for their direct marketing or other purposes, with affiliates and service providers that help us operate our business, to comply with the law or to respond to legal inquiries, as part of a corporate change like an acquisition or merger, and in other cases. To learn more about how we share your information and the choices you have, please click here.

You can review or request updates to the personal information that you have provided to us. To learn more about reviewing or updating your personal information, please click here.

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. We will post changes in this policy, and suggest that you periodically revisit this policy to stay informed of any changes.

We may permit third-party services to collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites including to provide more relevant ads to you across the Internet. To learn more about this practice and the choices that you can make, please click here.

If you have questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#bad3d4dcd5fad3d4decfc9cec8c3ded3ccdf94d9d5d7).

### Data Collection

_Personal Information_

When accessing our Properties, you may voluntarily provide personal information during your visit or by contacting us. We may collect this information when you visit our site to read or download information, as well as when you sign up for our newsletters. We may also receive personal information about you from third parties, such as partners, affiliates, service providers, and subsidiaries. We may combine this information with the information that you provide to us.

The personal information that we collect and store may include the following information about you:

Contact information, including your first and last name, email address, and phone number;   
Occupation information, including your company name, your title, and any other information you directly provide to us via our registration form.

_Non-Personal Information_

When you use our Properties we may collect various non-personal information, including, but not limited to, the date and time you access our Properties, the website from which you linked to our Property, IP address, Web pages visited, links clicked, your operating system and browser type, and your mobile device identifier. Such information is used for a variety of purposes such as operating and improving our Properties, analyzing demographic and statistical research about website usage, customizing offers, and to monitor the Properties for compliance with our terms of service and the law, as well as other purposes.

This non-personal information may be collected through various technologies, including but not limited to cookies and web beacons. To learn more about the use of this information, please see the interest-based advertising section below.

_Location Information_

We may also collect geolocation data pertaining to your mobile device, which may be linked to a device identifier or IP address. We may use this information to provide our services to you and to provide more relevant advertising content to you on our Properties. If you do not want to provide your location to us, please use the settings available on your mobile device to limit this sharing. Please note that if you limit sharing of geolocation data, certain features of the mobile application may not work.

Third _Parties_

We may use analytics services provided by third parties, including Google Analytics. To learn more about how Google Analytics collects and processes data and the choices Google may offer to control these activities, you may visit http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/.

We may also permit third parties to collect information on our Properties and combine that information with information collected on other non-affiliated websites or applications over time to personalize advertising. Please see below for more information on this practice and your choices.

### Data Use

We may use both personal and non-personal information that we collect from you for the purposes provided in this policy. Among other uses, we may use your information in the following ways:

  * To operate, maintain, and improve our Properties, including to maintain security;
  * If you identify yourself by sending us an e-mail containing personal information, to respond to your message;
  * To provide you with more relevant advertising content;
  * For our statistical, research, recordkeeping, and reporting purposes;
  * For our own marketing purposes;
  * To personalize and improve your experience of our Properties;
  * To monitor our Properties for compliance with our Terms of Service; and
  * For any other purpose identified at the point of collection.

### Data Sharing

We may share personal information:

  * With third parties, including for their direct marketing purposes (please see below for your choices related to this sharing);
  * With our affiliates and with service providers that help us operate our business;
  * With government entities as needed to provide our services and where required by law; 
  * As part of an acquisition or merger with another company, a partial or total sale of assets, or another corporate change, including at bankruptcy;
  * Pursuant to a subpoena, court order, or other legal process;
  * To investigate, respond to or resolve problems or inquiries (including law enforcement requests) or protect, enforce, or defend our rights, assets and/or interests;
  * To prevent or respond to a violation of any law, regulation, or our Terms of Service; or
  * With your consent or as otherwise disclosed at the time of collection.

### Your Choices

As noted above, we may disclose your information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you would like to opt out of such disclosures, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

When we send email messages, we include our address, contact information, and a link that you can use to unsubscribe from future messages. You can also go directly to your account profile to manage your subscription preferences.

### Update Personal Information

If you wish to review or update the personal information you have previously provided to us, such as your name or email address, please visit your account profile (which is linked from each of our newsletter emails) to request changes to your personal information.

### Third Party Websites

Our Properties may contain links to third-party websites or mobile applications. Please be aware that we do not control these linked websites and that this Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of any third-party property that you visit before you provide any information to that property’s owner.

### Interest-Based Advertising

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Properties. These companies may collect information about your visits to our Properties and other websites and/or apps in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. We may also partner with ad networks and other companies that serve ads on behalf of us and others on non-affiliated digital properties. Some of those ads may be personalized, meaning that they are intended to be relevant to you based on information these ad networks collect about your visits to our Properties and other non-affiliated web sites or apps over time. In connection with this activity, we adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) Self-Regulatory Principles.

You may visit www.aboutads.info/choices to learn more about interest-based advertising and how to opt-out of this form of advertising on your web browser by companies participating in the DAA self-regulatory program.

If you wish to opt-out of interest based advertising in mobile apps on your device by companies that participate in the DAA’s AppChoices app, you may download that app onto your device and exercise your choice. AppChoices is available at the links below:

You may also be able to limit data collection by third parties by using your mobile device settings. Please note that electing to opt out will not stop advertising from appearing in your browser or applications. It may make the ads you see less relevant to your interests. Additionally, please note that if you use a different browser or erase cookies from your browser, or use a different mobile device, you may need to renew your opt-out choices.

### Children

Our Properties are not intended for children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. We will post changes in this policy, and suggest that you periodically revisit this policy to stay informed of any changes.

### Security

We take reasonable measures to help protect data we collect from unauthorized access and use.

### Contact Us

If you have questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#2f464149406f46414b5a5c5b5d564b46594a014c4042).
